B06902100 - Calvin (劉益瑋)

Like usual, execute makefile using make and then proceed as described 
in the specs file.

I finished all of the tasks, albeit it's quite late and I can't
guarantee the correctness (especially for bidding_system_EDF).
//I only test the code with the given sample case, and it's correct

NOTE: When executing bidding_system_EDF, sometimes this message might pop out:
使用者定義的訊號1. In that case, please first delete the existing customer_log
and bidding_system_log inside the directory, and then try executing it again.

NOTE: bidding_system_EDF take around 5-10 seconds to execute.